<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[NAHJ Bay Area]]></title><description><![CDATA[The professional publishing platform]]></description><link>http://nahjbayarea.com</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 06:22:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[General Meeting + Mixer]]></title><description><![CDATA[Join us for a general meeting, learn about what we have been up to, some announcements and stick around for a small mixer. Will be at El…]]></description><link>http://nahjbayarea.com/a-full-style-test/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://nahjbayarea.com/a-full-style-test/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 07:03:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Join us for a general meeting, learn about what we have been up to, some announcements and stick around for a small mixer. Will be at El Tecolote starting from 6pm - 8:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sacramento Bee selects Angel Guerrero as its NAHJ Bay Area 2018 Intern]]></title><description><![CDATA[The National Association of Hispanic Journalists Bay Area chapter is proud to announce that the  Sacramento Bee  has once again turned to…]]></description><link>http://nahjbayarea.com/sacbee-intern/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://nahjbayarea.com/sacbee-intern/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 02:05:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;The National Association of Hispanic Journalists Bay Area chapter is proud to announce that the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sacbee.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sacramento Bee&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; has once again turned to our organization to help fill one of its summer internship spots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/angelguerrerooo?lang=es&quot;&gt;Angel Guerrero&lt;/a&gt;, a Sacramento State senior and the sports editor at The State Hornet for a second year in a row,  will join the Sac Bee as part of the 10-week Jennifer Garza Memorial Internship, established between NAHJ Bay Area and the regional paper to honor the former and now deceased reporter who championed diversity in their newsroom. The internship goal is to give aspiring journalists the opportunity to gain a practical education, professional experience and a great time in the state’s capital.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scott Lebar, managing editor of the &lt;em&gt;Sacramento Bee&lt;/em&gt;, said that Guerrero came very highly recommend and after meeting him could see why.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I interviewed the kid. [He’s] really sharp,” Lebar adding that “I love that he goes to Sac State.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Born in Hayward and raised in Stockton, Guerrero studied general communications at San Joaquin Delta College, then transferred to Sacramento State to pursue his Bachelor’s in Journalism. His five-year goal is to cover high school sports in California for a newspaper publication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thank you so much!” Guerrero enthusiastically said by email. “I’m very excited for the opportunity to prove myself in a professional setting”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Funds for the Jennifer Garza Memorial Internship have been made possible by the continued support of Pacific Gas and Electric Company (PG&amp;#x26;E). The interns at the Sac Bee are assigned a mentor and get to listen to experts, from the publisher to investigative reporters, talk about the ever-changing world of journalism.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>